Right now, open your lips and begin to use your faith to put a demand.
Ask for God's sanctification.
Sanctify me, Lord. Come into my heart. Wash me with your precious blood. Save my soul, Lord.
Cleanse me with your precious blood.
Ask Him to cleanse you with His precious blood.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
[Amen!]
I believe your heart is right now the temple, the altar, in Jesus Christ's name.
Amen!
You may be seated.
Hallelujah!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
There is a very important issue we need to know.
It's not only when the man of God attends to you in person.
When the man of God is attending to someone and you are there, and you are seeing what is happening,
your faith grows, more than even the person the man of God is attending to,
because you have the time to listen.
Opportunity to listen to what the man of God is saying,
to understand what the man of God is even saying, better than the person he is attending to.
This is how to build faith with what you are seeing everyday.
And most of you that watch Emmanuel TV, it is a gracious blessing,
especially when you are in a place where an anointed man of God is preaching,
or delivering a message and you are there sitting down watching,
or healing or prophesying, telling people something that is so awesome.
You are also surprised how a human can know all this. You that are listening - they are faith builders.
Nothing can build faith than that.
Looking at a man of God, praying for a sick one who is crying for help,
and you are there when he walks towards him and prays for him,
and the sick man stands up and starts walking. Ha!
That is a faith builder.
Tell your neighbour, 'Faith builder'.
[Faith builder]
I can't hear you.
And you need this faith to put a demand.
It is by faith you can say to God 'I'm sick'.
It is the also by faith you can say to the man of God,
'Man of God, please I'm sick. Pray for me'. It is by faith.
You can't just come to your senses or feeling to say, 'Man of God, pray for me. I am sick'.
There is nothing like that in the Bible.
You can only say it by faith.
So, we put a demand on the anointing by faith.
You need that faith. That is why the Bible says only faith pleases Him.
It means there is nothing you can do with Him without faith.
By faith, we put a demand on the anointing of God.
The testimony you have been hearing is just enough to take you there.
When it is time like this, it is time to pay attention - attention with devotion.
How do we pay attention to this?
You also have to be in an attitude of prayer.
Like I'm taking to you now, you are supposed to be praying.
Viewers all over the world, wherever you are, as you are looking,
paying attention to what I am saying, be in an attitude of prayer.
Continue to pray.
Simple language - we have given you some words that have been anointed.
"Lord Jesus, take more of me", this word has been anointed for a long time.
The Lord gave you that language. It is for you and it has been anointed.
"Take more of me, give me more of you, Lord Jesus.
Take more of me - more of your purity, more of your holiness".
As you are talking, your lips should not move.
It's not going to disturb your attention and concentration.
Do you know that as I am talking to you, I am praying? Ha!
As I am talking to you, I am praying.
Why?
This word is passing through two natures - from Prophet to Mr. T.B. Joshua to you.
You can not see that Prophet but you can see Mr T.B. Joshua.
Prophet is taking it from God, and Prophet is giving it to T.B. Joshua and T.B. Joshua is telling you - this is it.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
So, what are we saying?
When you are listening, you have a role to play.
Not just to pay attention - to be in an attitude of prayer.
To pay attention with devotion is to be in an attitude of what? Prayer.
So, now a word has been anointed for a long time.
"Take more of me and give me more of you - more of your holiness, purity, faithfulness, kindness."
Continue to say that.
This is the time for you to learn how to pray in the spirit.
You don't know how to pray in the spirit.
All the prayer you know how to pray is "In the name of Jesus, in the name of Jesus, in the name of Jesus."
This is what you are used to.
Like I am standing looking at you, I am praying -
that is Spirit prayer.
Oftentimes, "In the name of Jesus" is saying words, not praying prayer.
There are two.
It is not everybody that says, "In the name of Jesus, Jesus, Jesus" that is praying; many are saying words.
This is why it becomes so tense; because we engage our physical appearance - ourselves.
Because the Spirit prayer does not need [punching with hands]
If Spirit prayer, prayer by the Holy Ghost, needs [our physical appearance],
we need to go everywhere before the prayer is answered.
How can we stand here and send the prayer to the U.S., and the prayer is answered there immediately?
No it means it does not need this [punching with hands]
If it needs this [punching], we have to travel to the United States to get it to happen.
You can have that faith that moves mountains, if you pay attention.
That is, pray as you are listening to me.
Be in an attitude of prayer.
There are many things you are entitled to as I am talking to you.
Many things you are entitled to: One, you are supposed to be seeing things of celestial, vision,
seeing the immaterial world.
As you are looking at me, you should be seeing the forces behind this man. What is within? What is outside?
But you cannot see anything; you are only seeing a man talking to you.
That is why it is always difficult for you to believe.
If it's just this man that is talking you are looking at, it will be very difficult for you to believe.
For your belief to have a foundation, you must see beyond this appearance and you must see that vision.
Even before coming here, you are supposed to know much about this man, even before coming here.
It's only difficult when just a man like you, having appearance,
a similar appearance, every appearance you have he has, is now talking to you.
We have been to the university, we have lecturers, we have professors.
I mean, he will look like a lecturer to you, "This man is lecturing me".
Unless you see beyond this appearance.
When you see beyond this appearance, the job is half done.
The job is half done.
"Let us pray" - whether you have faith or not, you begin to pray.
This is what Christianity has turned to, and Christianity says you must have faith to pray
because if you do not have faith and you are praying,
by what authority would you put a demand on the anointing?
When you don't have faith, and you are now praying to God,
okay, by what medium, by what authority would you put a demand on the anointing?
This means you are using a net to fetch water.
Mark 5, verse 34.
"He said to her, 'Daughter, your faith has healed you.
Go in peace and be freed from your suffering'.
That shows that faith releases healing anointing.
Faith releases blessing anointing.
Faith releases deliverance, faith releases breakthrough.
What you are looking for - faith releases it.
He said, 'Go, your faith has healed you. Be freed from your suffering'.
We all regard faith as a Heavenly currency.
The more currency you have, the more Heavenly resources you purchase.
You agree with me?
Are you praying with your heart?
Simple prayer - "Take more of you, give me more of you." This is to fortify you, to overhaul you.
"Take more of me, give me more of your holiness, more of your righteousness, more of your purity."
Continue that. The Lord will take it up and will be saying it for you.
Then, your faith will begin to grow and grow.
You have more Heavenly currency to purchase Heavenly resources.
We don't just listen to the Gospel; we listen to the Gospel by being in an attitude of prayer.
When you are at home, and you tune your channel to a Christian channel,
and you hear a preacher preaching, immediately, you too begin to pray.
If not, what he's saying, will enter here and go here.
Like I am talking to you now, you must be in attitude of prayer, "Take more of me, give me more of you.
Take more of me, give me more of you, give me more of your faithfulness,
more of your obedience, more of your holiness, Lord.
Give me more of your holiness, give me more of your purity". So you begin to . . .
As you are saying it, you will just see your heart open,
and when your heart opens, you will begin to see me by your heart, you see visions.
You can only see visions when you see something with your heart,
but with your eyes you cannot see any vision.
You know, your heart is the prayer room. Your heart is the temple of God.
You want to see visions? You must see with your heart.
Inner my heart. Lord, I want to be like Jesus. Inner my heart.
Are you praying?
You must learn how to pray in the Spirit.
If you are a type that prays, like okay, you want to catch a flight, you are at the airport,
you will minimize talking to people because your time to talk to people is the time to pray.
You must create time for yourself.
Everywhere can be an altar. Altar of God - everywhere. When you sit down, you begin to [pray].
When you enter the plane, immediately you are entering, you start praying too.
When you sit down, you begin to pray.
Satan will not catch you unprepared
because the situation we face today is that satan keeps catching people unprepared.
Look at your dream. At the time you want to shout Jesus, satan has finished with you.
Okay, this is a good example. This is a crisis and I don't know.
It is like a blind man wanted to cross, but no Jesus.
I'm suddenly falling, and if I am now falling down, and say, "Jesus! Jesus!" No, it is for a selfish reason.
You want Him to save you; that is why you are calling Him.
But if Jesus has been part of me here, "Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus",
then He will save me because He has been the source of my life not because of a situation.
That is what we are facing now.
Start it now! That is the secret of my life.
As I am talking to you now, I am praying. When I am eating, I do pray. I am used to that.
When you have a certain time that you pray, satan will catch you before that time.
He has his own strategy and tactic, and he uses it.
What you started today will be very very difficult at the beginning,
but know you are playing your role before Jesus comes to play His own.
Do not give up.
Faith is a vacuum that draws the anointing from Jesus,
and that faith you are building now, the best faith builder is what you started now.
Prayer in the Spirit, "Take more of me, give me more of you".
Even self-healing will happen.
You will be very surprised that there is sickness you have been talking about,
and suddenly you wake up and find out that it's gone!
Yes, it will happen!
Brother, can I ask you a question?
What are you saying in your heart, tell the world.
"Oh Holy Spirit, take more of me, give me more of you, more of your strength, more of your companion,
more of your Holiness. Oh Holy Spirit, take more of me and give me more of you."
And you are saying it now now? As you are looking at me, you are engaging in it?
You are saying it? And do you promise to continue this?
Yes, sir.
You need to try what you have never tried before to get something to change your life.
Sit down, sir.
It's a revelation for you. I am pointing you to the way of success.
I want you to stand up now to make this covenant, that this is what you need to be doing now.
And there is a word that as been anointed for you, '"Take more of me, give me more of you,
more of your faithfulness, more of your kindness, more of your goodness and more of your self-control".
If you are able to do this without your lips moving, without your body moving,
without people around you knowing that you are praying, the sky is your limit.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
We have to make a covenant now; a promise to God.
Are you praying now?
By the time you start this, very soon, you cannot stop it. Something will continue.
Do you know blood? The way blood runs in your body?
That is the way the prayer will be running in your heart.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
But you must start it first.
Just like Peter said to Jesus, "I want to come with you".
"Let me see your faith first." That is Jesus for you.
That is, let me see your faith means begin your coming; I will help you.
He does not just walk to you and says ''Be healed!" He wants you to show your faith first.
Jesus always wants to give us what we do not know how to do so that He can teach us.
Tell your neighbour:
"Jesus always wants to give us what we do not know how to do so that He can teach us".
His instruction is always what you don't know how to do so that He Himself can teach us.
This is exactly what applies to the prayer.
If you know when Jesus will answer you, you will only pray at that time.
But since you don't know exactly when He will hear you, you keep praying. Very interesting.
That is why He is God.
He is always giving us what we don't know how to do so that He Himself can teach us.
This is why He said, "I will make you fishers of men, fishers of men, fishers of men".
If you know how to do that fishing, He doesn't need to show you.
Peter was walking along. When Peter got to a certain level of the water and the water swallowed him,
and he realized that he is about to drown, it was only his hand that we could see up.
But Jesus realized that he insisted. Instead of going back, he was going forward.
You know when you are about to drown, you are to run back.
But instead of Peter to run back, he continued and persisted.
Jesus said, "Oh no, this is genuine willingness".
He stretched his hand and said, "Here is my help."
The SCOAN Sunday Service
"Here is my help", and immediately Peter floated on the sea without a life jacket.
Imagine without a life jacket he floated on the sea.
In the same way, what is good for Peter is good for you.
So yes, your genuine willingness is needed.
Start it now. "Take more of me, give me more of you" - this is the only way.
No matter the miracle and blessing you receive here, to maintain them, you need Jesus.
Anybody can receive miracles, but not anyone can maintain them.
In the same vain, all the blessings you have at home: you have cars, you have this,
you were once a millionaire, you were this and that. You are unable to maintain them.
Maintenance is what we are talking about; it is not the blessing.
The blessing of God given to you; how to maintain them in the face of challenges.
"Take more of me, give me more of you."
You move with the Kingdom of God, you move with Heaven all the time but you do not know.
You keep asking for Heaven, but Heaven is with you; you move with Heaven.
You say, "Jesus, Jesus, Jesus". Where is Jesus? Jesus is with you.
Your heart. My heart is Heaven.
"Take more of me, give me more of you.
Lord Jesus, more of your faithfulness, more of your kindness, goodness, self-control.
In Jesus' name."
[Amen!]
Let me pray with you, raise up your hand.
Nothing shall take you from this promise.
[Amen!]
You are standing today to promise before God that His Word will continue to run in your heart!
His word will continue to run in your heart!
[Amen!]
Yes, His Word will continue to run in your spirit!
In Jesus Christ's name we pray!
[Amen!]
Yes, His Word will continue to run in your heart.
Prayer is the key, prayer is the key.
Prayer is the master key.
Jesus started with prayer and ended with prayer.
Simple! He started with prayer and ended with what? Prayer.
It means 24/7, you have to be in an attitude of what? Prayer.
To be in an attitude of prayer means in the heart. Heart means spirit. Like you are looking at me now,
Your mouth is not moving.
A good example for the viewers all over the world. Can you see the woman?
She's praying Spirit prayer in her heart.
"Take more of me, give me more of you."
How are you, mum?
I'm fine, daddy.
You are still praying? Does "How are you" stop you from praying?
No.
How are you? I'm fine, thank you.
Are you okay? I am fine, thank you, sir.
Have you taken your breakfast? Yes, daddy.
Does this stop your prayer? No, daddy.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Viewers all over the world, this is what we are talking about.
What we're used to, we Christians today -
Good afternoon, daddy. How are you, daddy?
Oh I am sorry, I am sorry, I was in the ..., you know.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Ok, you talk to me again.
Good afternoon, daddy. How are you?
The SCOAN Sunday Service
This is hypocrisy.
We love to be seen, we love to be noticed, we love attention.
You see my situation now, the way I walk, you greet me
because I want you to see me. This is what you people do outside there.
Good afternoon, daddy. How are you?
I'm not fine.
I am sorry, daddy.
Okay, I am okay now because of that sorry.
This is attention we love and this keeps destroying us. It is not good.
Can you see our mother here now?
She is in an attitude of prayer, and that is the prayer that breaks the yoke.
24/7 when you are going on the street.
Okay, move to the camera and begin to pray in your heart.
How are you? I'm fine, daddy? Continue again.
That is the life you should begin to live from now.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
That is the only way.
[Trust and Obey]
The word "trust" means 24/7.
There is no break in trust.
That is why the word trust is stronger - no break.
When you say, "I trust this thing", it means 24/7.
If you trust Jesus 24/7, the prayer you are used to today,
it is because you cannot exercise this kind of prayer while you are walking.
"In Jesus' name, in Jesus' name, Amen, in Jesus' name, Amen, in Jesus' name."
We must shout, we must make noise, we must let people know we are praying.
This is the kind of prayer we are used to, and that cannot work on the street.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
When you continue this spiritual battle, I am giving you five days. Wait.
What will happen, you will begin to speak in a new tongue; it will just come.
You will receive your right; what you deserve. You deserve excellence.
From now until Friday. Write it down, madam, you will come and give testimony.
I am using this woman as a good example to the whole world.
Viewers at home, you start it now. Start it now!
What are you saying in your heart? Tell us!
"Jesus, have more of me and let me have more of you; more of your goodness,
more of your faithfulness, more of your love, more of your peace."
Don't let any challenges stop you from saying that.
Even as you begin this journey now, there will be a lot of challenges
because if satan knows that you are about to get out of his way, he will bring a lot of challenges;
big challenges to stop you.
When your heart is disturbed, you can't say anything. Refuse to be disturbed.
By Friday or Saturday, you will just find that you are not praying,
but something is just praying, like a blood flowing in your heart.
You wait here in the church until next Saturday because I want to witness that promise.
I am talking to everyone here. I am talking to the viewers all over the world.
STANDARD FOR LIFE